# AKOREDE DEBORAH TEMITOPE

No 8, Adejumo Street, Elewura Challenge, Ibadan. temikorede97@gmail.com

## 07081752405, 08023651579

#### **BIO DATA**

**Gender:** Female **Date of Birth:** March 9<sup>th</sup> 1999

Religion: Christianity Marital Status: Single

L.G.A: Oluyole State of Origin: Oyo

Nationality: Nigerian

#### **VISION**

Proven work experience To contribute responsible skills, time, energy and technical support in the field through unfeigned and unwavering commitment towards achieving the goals of the organization and performing varieties of organizational procedures, technological and technical tasks where my skills and technical abilities can be utilized and efficiently contributed for the overall growth of the organization and to build my professional career. Strong financial background with experience in financial modeling, strategic minded with strong analytical and problem solving skills outstanding communication and interpersonal abilities.

#### **MISSION**

To create awareness and be a Pacesetter in this fast and ever tasking environment and to advance rapidly in the organization.

#### **VALUE**

- ➤ Goal oriented, efficiency, teamwork, honesty and reliable,
- Organizational skills and ability to manage deadlines.
- ➤ Ability to learn fast and work under pressure
- ➤ Willingness to learn
- > Pleasant and friendly disposition
- Excellent logical, analytic and computational skills
- > Strong, motivational and team player with excellent leadership skills

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION	WITH	DATE
HND (ACCOUNTING)		2018-2021
ND (ACCOUNTING)		2015-2017
S.S.C.E		2009-2015
F.S.L.C		2004-2009

SCHOOL ATTENDED	WITH	DATE
The oke ogun Polytechnic, saki		2018-2021
The oke ogun Polytechnic, saki		2015-2017
Ijaye High School		2009-2015
Omowumi Nursery & Primary School		2004-2009

## INFORMATION AND TECHNOLOGY SKILL

Micro-soft Word; Excel; and Power Point

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Excellent Brian Academy

Position: Teacher

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)

Benin, Edo State.

December 2021-October 2022

# Lysoplus Helathcare Ltd

Position: Sales Resp.

Ibadan, Oyo State.

May 2021 - September 2021

#### RESPONSIBILITIES

- \* Receiving and forwarding of drugs
- ❖ Monitoring and taking inventory on a regular basis
- ❖ Follows all standard in receiving stocks
- . Ensuring that drug are properly distributed at the pharmacy

## **HOBBIES**

Reading, writing. Singing and dancing

# REFERENCES

# Mrs Ajayi Oluwakemi

Fisco Nigeria Ltd.

Akure,

Ondo State.

+234 - 8062494724

# Damilare Ishola

**FETS** 

Ibadan Electricity Distribution Company

Ibadan.

+234-8102416978